SUBASH RADHAKRISHNAN

DEVOPS ENGINEER

- +91 7397638855
- subashradhakrishnan03@gmail.com



EXPERIENCE

ASM Technologies Limited.

Jan 2023 - Till date

TATA Consultancy Services Limited.

Nov 2020 - Dec 2022

DEVOPS ENGINEER

- Working in Agile methodology(SCRUM and KANBAN boards) using ServiceNOW tool.
- Monitored automated build and continuous software integration process using Jenkins.
- Worked on configuration management tool such as Ansible and made deployments using playbook and also Containerized using Docker as well.
- Having hands-on experience in Gitbash and Github and Bitbucket.
- Having hands-on experience in Linux administration.
- Initiated triggers and workflows in Universal Automation Center(UAC).
- Continuously monitored servers using Prometheus and Grafana tools.
- Also performed code quality check using SonarQube.
- Automation of workflow using bash and python scripting.

EDUCATION

2016 - 2020
SASTRA UNIVERSITY
Bachelor of Electrical and Electronics Engineering
2014 - 2016
ARR Higher Secondary School

SUMMARY

Flexible professional with experience developing and building IT solutions.

Confident DevOps Engineer with exemplary expertise in routine application maintenance tasks, including troubleshooting and testing.

Experienced in testing and implementing infrastructure and applications. Having around 2 years of experience using source control tools and maintaining CI/CD pipeline. Consistent team player with exemplary multitasking skills.

SKILLS

- Github
- Jenkins
- Ansible
- Docker
- AWS(EC2, IAM, S3, LAMBDA, Cloud Formation, Load balancer, Auto-scaling)
- Azure DevOps
- Linux Shell Scripting
- Python Scripting

CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft Azure Fundamentals